getawaytoday.com 2017-02-16

# Privacy Policy

### Get Away Today Discount Family Vacations Privacy Notice

Effective April 27, 2000

#### Our Commitment To Privacy:

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

#### The Information We Collect:

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the Get Away Today Vacations website. On some pages, you can order products, make requests, and register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages include but are not limited to: Name, Address, Email address, Phone number, and Credit/Debit Card Information.

#### The Way We Use Information:

We use the information you provide about yourself when placing an order only to complete that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order.

We use return email addresses to answer the emails we receive and promotional offers. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties.

We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and to share with advertisers. For example, we may tell an advertiser that X number of individuals visited a certain area on our website, or that Y number of men and Z number of women filled out our registration form, but we would not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals.

Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.

#### Our Commitment To Data Security:

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

#### Our Commitment To Children's Privacy:

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13.

#### How To Contact Us:

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please call us at 855-GET-AWAY or [click here](mailto:getaway@getawaytoday.com) to send us an e-mail.

Call us at 1-855-GET-AWAY

© 2017 Get Away Today Vacations As to Disney photos, logos, properties: ©Disney HARRY POTTER characters, names and related indicia are © & ™ Warner Bros. Entertainment Inc. Harry Potter Publishing Rights © JKR. (s16) ©2016 Universal Studios. All Rights Reserved. Dr. Seuss properties TM & © 2016 Dr. Seuss Enterprises, L.P. All rights reserved.
